



Phone

+963 937 731 517



a.jabban2000@gmail.com



Address

Damascus, Syria



Portfolio

abdulrahman-aljabban.github.io/ portfolio



SKILLS

Laravel PHP

MySQL

System analysis

RESTful API

OOP

HTML & CSS

Git

MS Office



LANGUAGE

Arabic: Mother tongue

English: Reading

Writing

Speaking =

ABDUL-RAHMAN **AL-JABBAN**

BACK-END WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE

As a Laravel developer, I thrive on creating well-structured projects with clean code. In 2020, my journey began during my graduation project. Over the years, I've gained valuable experience working on various projects and refactoring existing code, for different companies.



EDUCATION

2020 - Present



Technical Computer College

Damascus University, Syria

Department of Software Engineering

The graduation project was a Health care Web Application that Digitize hospitals data and configured an api for a pill reminder mobile application.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Laravel Software Developer

2023/02 - Present



TrendDXB | United Arab Emirates

- I made an e-commerce web application
- I analysed an employment platform project and designed it's database



Laravel Software Developer

2022/07 - 2023/02

Limitless Group | Syria

- I made a CV maker Web Application including analyzing the project and making its database and building APIs for the front-end.



Laravel Software Developer

2021/10 - 2022/07

InSoft-Online | Germany

- I made a Time Tracking Web Application including analysing the project and making it's database and design.
- I made a task management web application including analysing the project and making it's database.
- I configured an API for Mobile store application.
- I configured an API for a booking system.

(T)

SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE

.	PHPstorm	VS Code
	Github	Jira
	SQL Server	PHPmyAdmin
	Postman	Xampp/Wamp
	MS Teams	Windows